<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title><![CDATA[Trail running - Ultrarunning - Fastpacking - Thru-hiking - Supported - Unsupported - Self-supported - All of the Above]]></title>
        <description><![CDATA[Trail running - Ultrarunning - Fastpacking - Thru-hiking - Supported - Unsupported - Self-supported - All of the Above]]></description>
        <link>https://thegrid.ai/ultrapedestrian/</link>
        <generator>The Grid</generator>
        <lastBuildDate>Fri, 22 Jul 2016 05:03:11 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <atom:link href="https://thegrid.ai/ultrapedestrian/rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Dharma Bumming the Double Desolation Route]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>Dharma Bumming the Double Desolation Route</h1><p>Once the restriction of running only during daylight hours is a concept of the past, an adventure can begin at any time of the day or night. My adventure partner Lisa and I discovered this when we completed the Methow Trails 200k Nordic Ski Challenge, the first people to take it on in one push. We set out on a cold, starlit night at 11:00 p.m. to begin the ski challenge. We skied day and night to complete 217k of trail, sleeping in Lisa’s pop-up camper at the trailheads as needed for breaks. We had run and hiked together before, overnight, napping trailside when we started falling asleep on our feet. Staggering around like drunks becomes dangerous on certain types of trail. We usually choose rugged, remote trails, sometimes with precipitous drops to one side. So we have learned to grab sleep as needed in order to complete long endurance efforts together, and to begin them when it best works out for our busy schedules. </p></article>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/ultrapedestrian/dharma-bumming-the-double-desolation-route/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">cc053757-c82a-4723-94d6-268b2d51a060</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 20 Jul 2016 14:52:43 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>